next question so it's still difficulty
level one this time we're going to label
each reaction as E1 or E2 let's do the
same thing what are you thinking I want
to say it's E2 why cuz once again strong
base mhm they both have like trary or
secondary that like would work for
either but I think that's like the
biggest one that I can think of that is
and then yes you're right the fact that
this is secondary go ahead and label
what you think it is E2 the main reason
yep is because that is a strong base
that's really it I know that for E2 and
E1 it's really the same sort of
substrates that we're going to have main
difference is going to be the strong
base and weak base plus we could have
noticed the type solvent that we had
that would have been AIC that's true